What is the standard of high blood pressure?
The standard of high blood pressure is now
under the condition of using the lower pressure
three times a day to measure the actual blood pressure
We are using the actual blood pressure as the most classic standard of the standard
If the actual blood pressure is equal to 140
and the pressure of the blood pressure is equal to 90 mm
we can cut the high blood pressure
You must know that the pressure of the pressure is equal to 90
and not the same as the actual blood pressure
It is either over 140 or over 90
For example, I am 160 and 80 mm high blood pressure
We are high blood pressure patients
This is the standard of high blood pressure
And I am a young patient
My high blood pressure is not high, but 130 mm
and my low blood pressure is 100 mm
This is also the standard of high blood pressure
Remember that you cannot cut the blood pressure
only once
Because there are many reasons for this
For example, the effect of the white doctor
So you must emphasize the three times blood pressure
For example, recently we are taking new patients' vaccines
Many of our patients now have new patients
Because the new patient's vaccine is cooling blood pressure
It is high, you cannot hit it
It is very tense
In fact, I let him calm down
Because he is fighting new patients
Many people are very nervous
Let him calm down and test again
Blood pressure is not high
So do not be a real blood pressure once
Because the doctor is also a doctor to you
The doctor is giving you blood pressure
So he is also a real blood pressure
So our most important standard of the standard of the standard of the standard is 140
And what we just said
The standard of dynamic blood pressure is another kind of calculation
It is 24 hours of average blood pressure
High pressure 103 or low pressure of 80
In addition, the standard of our family self-criticism
Is more strict than real blood pressure
Our family self-criticism
High pressure is 135
Low pressure is 85
It can be a standard of high blood pressure
As long as it is not the same three times blood pressure
So this is our standard of high blood pressure